Translated by Doraemon
The sky in the dark, the sky in the dark
It's been a long day, so let's go on a picnic
I'll always be with you and always be with you
I'll always be with you, I'll always be with you
I'll always be with you, so let's go on a picnic
It's been a long day, so let's go on a picnic
Everyone, please be patient with your heart.
We'll have to do what I feel.
Ah ah ah ah ah yes!
What do you want?
What do you want to do?
Sniper
A lot!
Nimbly memories
Oh, Dad!
Hey!
Dad, you're...
Oh, Dad!
Ha, ha, ha!
It's really good!
I feel like I'm going back to normal!
Ha, ha, ha!
I'm going to hit you!
I was looking at you before, so it's my first time seeing you!
How was it? You're so smart!
I'm going to hit you!
Ha, ha, ha!
Huh?
It's so funny! I'm being bullied!
Oh, that's...
What are you doing?
Hey!
Are you okay, Kappu?
Hey, Kappu!
How are you?
Kappu!
Hey, Kappu!
All right!
Hey!
Have a lot of food!
I was surprised, Iba-chan.
Yeah, a little.
Why did you get beaten up?
I haven't come to this place for a long time.
That's why I don't have a chance to get beaten up.
Is that the black humor of that time?
That's right.
There's a reason why this place is like an innazuma.
That guy is making a new cap to the eye.
Kappu, maybe...
That's right.
This is that super cap.
That's right!
You were super-capped!
Dad, do you know this?
Yeah.
This guy is making a new cap to the center of the universe.
I've been talking about this for more than 10 years.
Hmm...
Ah!
It's so hot!
Why don't you want something like that?
It's Kappu's ninja!
Kappu!
Hey!
I was surprised.
Kappu is definitely not going to eat the first person.
Hey!
Is this the cap?
Yeah!
It was strong.
I'll keep going to the center of the universe.
I was thinking about going around as well.
I'm going to go around the corner of the universe.
I'll go around the corner of the universe,
super-capped!
Super-capped!
Kappu is super-capped!
So that was the first time I noticed the same way?
I knew it was a mistake.
I saw it.
Really?
I thought it was a mistake.
The following day,
we'll give it a shot.
I thought it was a mistake.
The last half is a mistake.
I think it's down there.
But that's not what it was like.
You know I saw it here.
It's been a while since I saw you in front of me.
Is that so?
Now, Eba-chan, eat the cake.
Yes!
Huh?
Where did you go before?
What?
Let's go!
What is it?
What? Stop!
I can't understand.
I can't handle it.
I can't handle, I can't handle.
R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R...
R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R...
R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R-R...
I was worried about him a lot.
And you worked hard on the horse?
Yeah. We all worked hard on it.
It's hard to see a lot of people who are always smiling at you.
That's right.
I wonder what I should have done if I didn't do it before.
Hey, don't you get it?
If you don't get it, you'll get it.
No way. I don't get it at all.
But I'm worried about that.
Hmm.
I'll call you if I'm late.
Eh?
Can't you eat all of the food?
Is that so?
Ah?
It seems like it's our past.
Ah...
If you say that...
Yes.
Well then...
Father.
The cap is...
I can't eat all of the food.
Only the person is close to me.
I can't be bothered.
Then, what will happen to the cap?
It's a delicate thing to do with the salad bread.
If you come to the hospital, you'll be in trouble.
That's right.
Shut up!
I'm sorry for you.
The cap is a bit weird.
The cap is weird.
I'm sorry for you yesterday.
That cap is a bit weird.
That cap is weird.
It's not weird.
I'm really sorry for you.
Is it weird?
It's weird.
What's wrong?
Eh?
Isn't it weird?
Is that so?
Really?
Yes.
I was too angry.
I knew that the cap was weird.
Is that so?
I didn't know.
I didn't know that.
It's weird.
What?
Is it weird?
It's weird.
When did you come to the hospital?
I came to the hospital.
What?
Yes.
I found it in the video.
Now let's see.
kuvve pen Jahren.
It's weird.
Look at this.
In short, the name of the pilgrimage.
This time, epsilonk, an Abandoned
was called Sferkapp.
Superkapp.
How about it?
It's a Superkapp.
I'm sure he lost his way!
You know, I've been using the electric car for years!
The season was the same, but
you could see the sun shining on your cheeks
and there's a lot of fans here!
And the sun's shining on your cheeks!
Superkaps! Superkaps!
You're really nervous, huh?
Now, let's do it!
The sun is shining!
Superkaps!
It's just a dog.
There's no way we can save a dinosaur.
Kamaka doesn't eat anything,
so I can't eat it.
It's so good.
I see.
You didn't have to eat like we were cooking today.
I'm not doing a good thing to eat,
Oh my god, you have to do that, too!
You're gonna do that, too!
Don't forget!
I will help you do that!
Eh, you're not...
I'm not!
NNN...
Are you alone?
Ben-chan!
What?
Uh, just a bit.
Please, Mr. Ho!
Huh?
Well then, Muka Muka-chan has prepared a special dish for you.
It looks delicious, isn't it?
It's delicious, isn't it?
Oh...
I've never seen such a delicious dish!
Muka Muka-chan!
I want to eat all of it!
You don't have to eat all of it, right?
What are you talking about?
You don't have to eat all of it, don't you?
You don't have to eat all of it, Mom.
Huh? What is that?
You don't have to eat all of it, Muka Muka?
That's right, that's right!
It's okay.
Muka Muka has prepared a special dish for you.
Muka Muka, if you want to eat, eat it.
Uiba, you...
Muka Muka Muka can't eat anything anymore.
It's much better than I thought.
Now, eat it.
Yes, yes!
Muka Muka Muka-chan!
It's delicious!
Muka Muka Muka...
What's wrong, Muka Muka?
Don't you have to eat all of it?
Muka...
Come here!
What do you say?
I should eat all of it.
I'm going to eat all of it.
Please eat all of it.
Oh, right.
What are you eating all of it?
No! That's not what I meant!
Oh! I'm done!
I'm done...
Hey, Muka Muka! Don't worry about it!
Alright! Good night!
Let's go meet Muka Muka again!
Huh? Really?
But, Yo-chan! Muka Muka Muka!
What? What's going on?
What's going on?
Muka Muka!
You guys like Muka Muka, right?
You guys like Muka Muka?
Muka Muka!
Hey! Muka Muka!
What are you doing?
Muka Muka!
Hey! Wait!
If you get to meet Muka Muka,
you'll be in a good mood.
Do you understand the meaning of the human language?
Muka Muka!
Huh? Muka Muka!
Can you bring me some milk?
I'm going to the post office.
Don't you know?
Muka Muka!
Do you eat fried chicken?
Hey! I'm sorry!
Father, I'm sorry for this move.
Don't worry about it.
What do you think?
I'm sorry for the cap.
I don't know what to eat for a week.
I did what I could do, but it's too late.
Is that so?
Muka Muka!
Look at me carefully.
Stop it!
It's okay.
Thank you, Muka Muka.
Muka Muka!
If you do that, you can become a fighter.
A fighter?
Yes, I'm the first fighter to have a good luck.
What? A good luck?
That's a good cap, right?
Yes, I brought it to the first time I got it.
I wanted to give you the future of the original of the archery.
That's right.
I'm not going to lose to other Hena Chokuma.
Well, that's right, but Yosoku, don't you have anything to do with it?
Huh?
Do I have a cap?
I think the cap looks cute, but...
Father, get the cap!
Get the cap!
All right.
Let's do it!
All right, let's do it!
Father, get the cap!
Oh, the cap!
Calm down.
What do you think?
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
I have a cap.
I'm sorry that I can't get the cap.
I can't get the cap.
Oh, oh!
I'm not scared.
You're the fastest.
If you run like this, you'll be able to run like this.
The cap!
I'll get the cap!
All right!
I'll get it!
All right, let's do the cap.
All right, let's do it!
Father, face me!
Show me the way you're doing!
Stop!
Show me your power!
I'm going to kill you!
Are you going to lose to the only you're doing?
You're going to lose to the only one?
Don't let him go!
No! No!
I did it, Kappu!
That's the Kappu Super Cup!
Translated by Releska
Wow...
ties...
around the fields...
uryx city-like city of the city
instead of cheap public art
Hello everyone
Now,
what did you say just now?
It's natural
So
it's because
it fits my mind
since it's heart
Bye, bye, bye, bye, bye
Let's get cinco
Move one more time
Come to the moon
Come to the next het splash
I'm gonna do it
Let's go! Let's go!
I've lost my mind!
I've lost my school, my school, my school, my school!
Are you planning to come to me with my time machine?
No way!
What is it? You friend?
I've lost my mind!
Ah! I'll come here!
Next time, I'll go to Mugamikapara Dice.
I'll go to Mugamikapara Dice.